wappalyzer.com 2019-04-16

# Wappalyzer - Privacy Policy

* * *

The Wappalyzer Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use Wappalyzer's products and services, including information provided when you use the Wappalyzer browser extension ('extension'). In addition, the following describes our privacy practices that are specific to the extension. 

### Information we collect

You do not need to provide any personal information in order to download and use the extension. All of the features can be used without sharing any personally identifiable information. 

The extension has some basic features that work automatically when you use the browser extension. Other features are optional and only operate and transmit data if you choose to have them enabled. 

### Basic features

Any time you use the extension to analyze a website, the extension sends basic, limited information including the domain name of the website you have visited and what application was identified on it. This data is retained in Wappalyzer's server logs and protected according to our general Privacy Policy but may be sold to or shared with our third party partners. At no time can this data be traced back to you personally, since no personally identifiable information is stored. 

### Information security

Any information sent to Wappalyzer will be maintained in accordance with the Wappalyzer Privacy Policy. Wappalyzer's Privacy Policy does not cover information that you send to third party sites. 

### Your choices

Any feature that works by automatically sending information about sites when you visit them can be disabled and re-enabled in the extension settings.
